Register of the William H. Rehnquist papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1969-2005
  The original order of the materials has been largely preserved: the correspondence is arranged chronologically as a succession of alphabetical files, with the time periods generally corresponding to the October to June terms.
  - Letters of condolence on the death of Natalie Cornell Rehnquist, 1991
    - A, 1991 (Box-folder 95: 1)
    - B, 1991 (Box-folder 95: 2-7)
    - C, 1991 (Box-folder 95: 8-9)
    - D, 1991 (Box-folder 96: 1-2)
    - E, 1991 (Box-folder 96: 3)
    - F, 1991 (Box-folder 96: 4-5)
    - G, 1991 (Box-folder 96: 6-7)
    - H, 1991 (Box-folder 96: 8-9)
    - I-J, 1991 (Box-folder 96: 10)
    - K, 1991 (Box-folder 97: 1-2)
    - L, 1991 (Box-folder 97: 3-4)
    - M, 1991 (Box-folder 97: 5-8)
    - N, 1991 (Box-folder 97: 9)
    - P-Q, 1991 (Box-folder 98: 1)
    - R, 1991 (Box-folder 98: 2-3)
    - S, 1991 (Box-folder 98: 4-7)
    - T, 1991 (Box-folder 98: 8)
    - U-V, 1991 (Box-folder 98: 9)
    - W-Z, 1991 (Box-folder 99: 1-2)
    - Replies, 1991 (Box-folder 99: 3)
  - Letters of congratulation on William H. Rehnquist's appointment as Chief Justice, 1986
    - A, 1986 (Box-folder 99: 2)
    - B, 1986 (Box-folder 99: 5-7)
    - C, 1986 (Box-folder 99: 8-9)
    - D, 1986 (Box-folder 100: 1)
    - E, 1986 (Box-folder 100: 2)
    - F, 1986 (Box-folder 100: 3)
    - G, 1986 (Box-folder 100: 4-5)
    - H, 1986 (Box-folder 100: 6-7)
    - I-J, 1986 (Box-folder 100: 8)
    - K, 1986 (Box-folder 100: 9)
    - L, 1986 (Box-folder 100: 10-11)
    - M, 1986 (Box-folder 101: 1-3)
    - N, 1986 (Box-folder 101: 4)
    - O, 1986 (Box-folder 101: 5)
    - P-Q, 1986 (Box-folder 101: 6-7)
    - R, 1986 (Box-folder 101: 8-9)
    - S, 1986 (Box-folder 101: 10-11)
    - T, 1986 (Box-folder 102: 1-2)
    - V, 1986 (Box-folder 102: 3)
    - W-Z, 1986 (Box-folder 102: 4-5)
  - Letters and cards of encouragement received during Justice Rehnquist's illness, 2004-2005
    - 2004 (Box-folder 102: 6-10)
    - 2004 (Box-folder 103: 1-8)
    - 2004 (Box-folder 104: 1-7)
    - 2005 (Box-folder 104: 8-11)
    - 2005 (Box-folder 105: 1-9)
  - Letters from average citizens, 1974-1976
    - 1974 (Box-folder 106: 1-2)
    - 1975-1976 (Box-folder 106: 3)
  - Memoranda, 1969-1980
    - Cannon, Mark W., 1977-1980 (Box-folder 106: 4)
    - Christmas parties, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 106: 5)
    - Conferences, 1976-1978
      - 1976 term (Box-folder 106: 6)
      - 1977 term (Box-folder 106: 7)
      - 1978 term (Box-folder 106: 8)
    - Recusal, 1972 (Box-folder 106: 9)
    - Travel, 1969-1979
      - 1969-1970 (Box-folder 106: 10)
      - 1972-1973 (Box-folder 106: 11)
      - 1974-1976 (Box-folder 107: 1)
      - 1977-1979 (Box-folder 107: 2)
    - Word processing, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 107: 3)
  - Moot court invitations and declinations, 1972-1979
    - 1972-1974 (Box-folder 107: 4)
    - 1975-1979 (Box-folder 107: 5)
  - General, 1972-1975
    - A, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 107: 6)
    - B, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 107: 7)
    - C, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 107: 8)
    - D, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 108: 1)
    - E, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 108: 2)
    - F, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 108: 3)
    - G, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 108: 4)
    - H, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 108: 5)
    - I, 1973 (Box-folder 108: 6)
    - J, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 108: 7)
    - K, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 108: 8)
    - L, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 108: 9)
    - M, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 109: 1)
    - N, 1972-1985 (Box-folder 109: 2)
    - O, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 109: 3)
    - P, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 109: 4)
    - Q, 1973 (Box-folder 109: 5)
    - R, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 109: 6)
    - S, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 109: 7)
    - T, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 109: 8)
    - U, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 110: 1)
    - V, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 110: 2)
    - W-Z, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 110: 3)
  - Seventh Circuit, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 110: 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 110: 5)
  - General, 1976-1979
    - A, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 110: 6)
    - B, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 110: 7)
    - C, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 110: 8)
    - D, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 111: 1)
    - E, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 111: 2)
    - F, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 111: 3)
    - G, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 111: 4)
    - H, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 111: 5)
    - I, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 111: 6)
    - J, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 111: 7)
    - K, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 111: 8)
    - L, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 112: 1)
    - M, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 112: 2)
    - N, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 112: 3)
    - O, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 112: 4)
    - P, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 112: 5)
    - Q, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 112: 7)
    - R, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 112: 8)
    - S, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 113: 1)
    - T, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 113: 2)
    - U, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 113: 3)
    - V, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 113: 4)
    - W, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 113: 5)
    - X-Z, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 113: 6)
  - Law clerks, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 113: 7)
  - General, 1980-1981
    - A, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 113: 8)
    - B, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 113: 9)
    - C, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 114: 1)
    - D, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 114: 2)
    - E, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 114: 3)
    - F, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 114: 4)
    - G, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 114: 5)
    - H, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 114: 6)
    - I, 1980 (Box-folder 115: 1)
    - J, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 115: 2)
    - K, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 115: 3)
    - L, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 115: 4)
    - M, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 115: 5)
    - N, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 115: 6)
    - O, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 115: 7)
    - P, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 115: 8)
    - Q, 1981 (Box-folder 116: 1)
    - R, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 116: 2)
    - S, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 116: 3)
    - T, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 116: 4)
    - U, 1981 (Box-folder 116: 5)
    - V, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 116: 6)
    - W, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 116: 7)
    - X-Z, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 116: 8)
  - General, 1982-1983
    - A, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 117: 1)
    - B, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 117: 2)
    - C, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 117: 3)
    - D, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 117: 4)
    - E, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 117: 5)
    - F, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 117: 6)
    - G, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 117: 7)
    - H, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 118: 1)
    - I, 1982 (Box-folder 118: 2)
    - J, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 118: 3)
    - K, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 118: 4)
    - L, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 118: 5)
    - M, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 118: 6)
    - N, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 118: 7)
    - O, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 118: 8)
    - P, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 118: 9)
    - Q, 1982 (Box-folder 119: 1)
    - R, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 119: 2)
    - S, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 119: 3)
  - General, 1984-1985
    - A, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 119: 4)
    - B, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 119: 5)
    - C, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 119: 6)
    - D, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 120: 1)
    - E, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 120: 2)
    - F, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 120: 3)
    - G, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 120: 4)
    - H, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 120: 5)
    - I-J, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 120: 6)
    - K, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 120: 7)
    - L, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 120: 8)
    - M, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 120: 9)
    - O, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 121: 1)
    - P, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 121: 2)
    - R, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 121: 3)
    - S, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 121: 4)
    - T, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 121: 5)
    - U, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 121: 6)
    - V, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 121: 7)
    - W, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 121: 8)
    - X-Z, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 121: 9)
  - General, 1986-1987
    - A, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 122: 1)
    - C, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 122: 2-3)
    - D, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 122: 4)
    - E, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 122: 5)
    - F, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 122: 6-7)
    - G, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 123: 1-2)
    - H, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 123: 3-4)
    - J, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 123: 5-6)
    - K, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 123: 7)
    - L, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 124: 1)
    - M, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 124: 2-3)
    - N, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 124: 4)
    - O, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 124: 5)
    - P, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 124: 6, Folder 125: 1)
    - Q, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 125: 2)
    - R, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 125: 3-4)
    - S, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 125: 5-8)
    - T, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 126: 1)
    - V, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 126: 2)
    - W, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 126: 3-5)
    - X-Z, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 126: 6)
  - Ferrari, Sue, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 126: 7)
  - General, 1987-1988
    - A, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 195: 1)
    - B, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 195: 2)
    - C, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 195: 3)
    - D, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 195: 4)
    - E, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 195: 5)
    - F, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 195: 6)
    - G, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 196: 1)
    - H, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 196: 2)
    - I, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 196: 3)
    - J, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 196: 4)
    - K, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 196: 5)
    - L, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 196: 6)
    - M, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 197: 1-2)
    - N, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 197: 3)
    - O, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 197: 4)
    - P, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 197: 5)
    - R, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 197: 6)
    - S, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 197: 7)
    - T, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 197: 8)
    - W, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 197: 9)
  - General, 1988-1989
    - A, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 127: 1)
    - B, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 127: 2)
    - C, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 127: 3)
    - D, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 127: 4)
    - E, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 127: 5)
    - F, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 127: 6)
    - G, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 127: 7)
    - H, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 128: 1)
    - I-J, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 128: 2)
    - K, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 128: 3)
    - L, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 128: 4)
    - M, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 128: 5)
    - N, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 128: 6)
    - O, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 128: 7)
    - P, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 128: 8)
    - Q, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 129: 1)
    - R, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 129: 2)
    - S, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 129: 3)
    - T, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 129: 4)
    - U, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 129: 5)
    - V, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 129: 6)
    - W-Z, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 129: 7)
  - Judges, 1988-1989
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 129: 8-9)
    - Letters of appointment, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 130: 1)
    - Requests for letters of appreciation, 1989 (Box-folder 130: 2)
    - Marshal's office, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 130: 3)
  - General, 1989-1990
    - A, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 130: 4)
    - B, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 130: 5)
    - C, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 130: 6)
    - D, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 130: 7)
    - E, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 130: 8)
    - F, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131: 1)
    - G, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131: 2)
    - H, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131: 3)
    - I, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131: 4)
    - J, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131: 5)
    - K, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131: 6)
    - L, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131: 7)
    - M, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131: 8)
    - N, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131: 9)
    - O, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131: 10)
    - P, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 131: 11)
    - R, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 132: 1)
    - S, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 132: 2)
    - T, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 132: 3)
    - U, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 132: 4)
    - V, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 132: 5)
    - W, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 132: 6)
    - Y, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 132: 7)
    - Z, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 132: 8)
  - General, 1990-1991
    - A, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 132: 9)
    - B, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 132: 10)
    - C, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 132: 11)
    - D, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 133: 1)
    - E, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 133: 2)
    - F, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 133: 3)
    - G, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 133: 4)
    - H, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 133: 5)
    - J, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 133: 6)
    - K, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 133: 7)
    - L, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 133: 8)
    - M, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 133: 9)
    - N, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 133: 10)
    - O, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 134: 1)
    - P, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 134: 2-3)
    - R, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 134: 4)
    - S, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 134: 5-6)
    - T, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 134: 7)
    - V, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 134: 8)
    - W, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 134: 9)
    - Y-Z, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 134: 10)
  - Memoranda, 1991-1992
    - 1991
      - May (Box-folder 135: 1)
      - June (Box-folder 135: 2)
      - July-August (Box-folder 135: 3)
      - September (Box-folder 135: 4)
      - October (Box-folder 135: 5)
      - November (Box-folder 135: 6)
      - December (Box-folder 135: 7)
    - 1992
      - June (Box-folder 135: 8-9)
      - September (Box-folder 136: 1-2)
      - October (Box-folder 136: 3)
  - General, 1992-1993
    - A, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 136: 4-5)
    - B, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 136: 6)
    - C, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 136: 7-8)
    - D, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 137: 1)
    - E, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 137: 2)
    - F, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 137: 3)
    - G, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 137: 4)
    - H, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 137: 5)
    - I-J, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 137: 6)
    - K, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 137: 7)
    - L, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 137: 8)
    - M, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 138: 1-2)
    - N, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 138: 3-4)
    - O, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 138: 5)
    - P, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 138: 6-7)
    - R, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 138: 8)
    - S, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 139: 1-3)
    - T, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 139: 4)
    - U-V, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 139: 5)
    - W, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 139: 6)
  - Supreme Court justices, 1992-1994
    - 1992 (Box-folder 139: 7)
    - 1993 (Box-folder 139: 8-9)
    - 1994 (Box-folder 139: 10)
  - General, 1993-1994
    - A, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 1)
    - B, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 2)
    - C, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 3)
    - D-E, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 4)
    - F, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 5)
    - G, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 6)
    - H, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 7)
    - I-J, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 8)
    - K, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 9)
    - L, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 10)
    - M, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 11)
    - N, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 12)
    - O, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 13)
    - P, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 140: 14)
    - R, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 141: 1)
    - S, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 141: 2-3)
    - T, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 141: 4)
    - V, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 141: 5)
    - W-Y, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 141: 6)
  - Federal Judicial Center, 1994-1995
    - 1994 (Box-folder 141: 7-8)
    - 1995 (Box-folder 141: 9-10)
  - General, 1994-1995
    - A, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 141: 11)
    - B, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 141: 12)
    - C, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 142: 1)
    - D, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 142: 2)
    - E, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 142: 3)
    - F, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 142: 4)
    - G, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 142: 5)
    - H, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 142: 6)
    - I-J, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 142: 7)
    - K, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 143: 1)
    - L, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 143: 2-3)
    - M, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 143: 4)
    - N, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 143: 5)
    - O, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 143: 6)
    - P-Q, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 143: 7)
    - R, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 143: 8)
    - S, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 143: 9, Folder 144: 1-2)
    - T, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 144: 3-4)
    - U-V, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 144: 5)
    - W, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 144: 6)
  - Supreme Court justices, 1994-1996
    - 1994 (Box-folder 144: 7-8)
    - 1995 (Box-folder 144: 9)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 144: 10)
  - Lantz, Robert, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 144: 11)
  - Law clerks, 1994-1996
    - 1994 (Box-folder 144: 12)
    - 1995 (Box-folder 145: 1)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 145: 2-3)
  - General, 1995-1996
    - A, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 145: 4)
    - B, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 145: 5-6)
    - C, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 145: 7-8)
    - D, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 145: 9)
    - E, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 145: 10)
    - F, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 146: 1)
    - G, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 146: 2)
    - H, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 146: 3-4)
    - I-J, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 146: 5)
    - K, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 146: 6)
    - L, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 146: 7)
    - M, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 146: 8-9)
    - N, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 147: 1)
    - O, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 147: 2)
    - P-Q, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 147: 3)
    - R, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 147: 4)
    - S, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 147: 5-6)
    - T, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 147: 7)
    - U-V, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 147: 8)
    - W, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 147: 9-10)
    - Y-Z, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 147: 11)
  - General, 1996-1997
    - A, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 148: 1)
    - B, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 148: 2-3)
    - C, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 148: 4)
    - D, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 148: 5)
    - E, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 148: 6)
    - F, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 148: 7)
    - G, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 148: 8)
    - H, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 148: 9)
    - I-J, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 148: 10)
    - K, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 148: 11)
    - L, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 149: 1-2)
    - M, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 149: 3)
    - N, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 149: 4)
    - O, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 149: 5)
    - P-Q, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 149: 6)
    - R, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 149: 7)
    - S, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 149: 8-9)
    - T, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 150: 1)
    - U-V, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 150: 2)
    - W, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 150: 3-4)
    - Y, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 150: 5)
  - General, 1997-1998
    - A, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 150: 6)
    - B, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 150: 7-8)
    - C, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 150: 9)
    - D, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 150: 10)
    - E, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 150: 11)
    - F, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 150: 12)
    - G, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 151: 1)
    - H, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 151: 2)
    - I-J, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 151: 3)
    - K, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 151: 4)
    - L, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 151: 5)
    - M, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 151: 6-7)
    - N, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 151: 8)
    - O, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 151: 9)
    - P-Q, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 151: 10)
    - R, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 151: 11)
    - S, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 151: 12, Folder 152: 1-2)
    - T, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 152: 3)
    - V, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 152: 4)
    - W, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 152: 5)
    - Y, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 152: 6)
  - General, 1998-1999
    - A, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 152: 7-8)
    - B, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 152: 9-10)
    - C, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 153: 1)
    - D, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 153: 2)
    - E, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 153: 3)
    - F, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 153: 4-5)
    - G, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 153: 6-7)
    - H, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 153: 8-9)
    - I-J, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 153: 10)
    - K, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 154: 1)
    - L, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 154: 2-3)
    - M, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 154: 4-5)
    - N, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 154: 6)
    - O, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 154: 7)
    - P-Q, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 154: 8-9)
    - R, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 155: 1-2)
    - S, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 155: 3-4)
    - T, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 155: 5)
    - V, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 155: 6)
    - W, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 155: 7)
    - Y, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 155: 8)
    - Z, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 155: 9)
  - Administrative Office of the United States Courts, 1999-2000
    - 1999 (Box-folder 156: 1-7)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 156: 8-10)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 157: 1-6)
  - General, 1999-2000
    - A, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 157: 7)
    - B, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 157: 8-9)
    - C, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 158: 1)
    - D, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 158: 2)
    - E, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 158: 3)
    - F, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 158: 4)
    - G, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 158: 5-6)
    - H, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 158: 7-8)
    - I-J, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 158: 9)
    - K, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 158: 10-11)
    - L, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 158: 12)
    - M, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 159: 1-2)
    - N, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 159: 3)
    - O, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 159: 4)
    - P-Q, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 159: 5)
    - R, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 159: 6-7)
    - S, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 159: 8-9)
    - T, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 159: 10)
    - W, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 160: 1-2)
  - General, 2000-2001
    - A, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 160: 3)
    - B, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 160: 4-5)
    - C, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 160: 6-7)
    - D, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 160: 8)
    - E, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 160: 9)
    - F, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 160: 10)
    - G, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 161: 1)
    - J, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 161: 2)
    - K, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 161: 3)
    - L, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 161: 4-5)
    - M, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 161: 6-7)
    - N, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 161: 8)
    - O, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 161: 9)
    - P, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 161: 10)
    - R, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 161: 11)
    - S, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 162: 1-2)
    - T, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 162: 3)
    - V, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 162: 4)
    - W-Y, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 162: 5)
  - General, 2001-2002
    - A, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 162: 6)
    - B, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 162: 7-8)
    - C, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 162: 9)
    - D-E, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 162: 10)
    - F, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 162: 11)
    - G, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 163: 1)
    - H, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 163: 2)
    - J, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 163: 3)
    - K, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 163: 4)
    - L, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 163: 5)
    - M, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 163: 6-7)
    - N, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 163: 8)
    - O, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 163: 9)
    - P-Q, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 163: 10)
    - R, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 163: 11)
    - S, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 163: 12-13)
    - T, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 164: 1)
    - U-V, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 164: 2)
    - W, 2001-1002 (Box-folder 164: 3)
  - General, 2002-2003
    - A, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 164: 4-5)
    - B, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 164: 6-7)
    - C, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 164: 8-9)
    - D, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 164: 10-11)
    - E, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 164: 12)
    - F, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 164: 13)
    - G, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 165: 1)
    - H, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 165: 2)
    - I-J, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 165: 3)
    - K, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 165: 4)
    - L, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 165: 5-6)
    - M, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 165: 7-8)
    - N, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 165: 9, Folder 166: 1)
    - O, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 166: 2)
    - P, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 166: 3-4)
    - R, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 166: 5-6)
    - S, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 166: 7-8)
    - T, 2002-003 (Box-folder 166: 9)
    - U-V, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 166: 10)
    - W, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 167: 1-2)
  - General, 2003-2004
    - A, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 167: 3-4)
    - B, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 167: 5)
    - C, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 167: 6)
    - D-E, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 167: 7)
    - F, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 167: 8)
    - G, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 167: 9)
    - H, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 168: 1)
    - I-J, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 168: 2)
    - K, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 168: 3)
    - L, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 168: 4-5)
    - M, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 168: 6-7)
    - N, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 168: 8-9)
    - O-P, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 168: 10)
    - R, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 169: 1)
    - S, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 169: 2-3)
    - T, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 169: 4)
    - U-V, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 169: 5)
    - W, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 169: 6)
  - Alumni Club, 2004 (Box-folder 169: 7)
  - General, 2004-2005
    - A, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 169: 8-9)
    - B, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 169: 10)
    - C, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 170: 1-2)
    - D-E, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 170: 3)
    - F, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 170: 4)
    - G, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 170: 5)
    - H, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 170: 6)
    - I-J, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 170: 7)
    - K, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 170: 8)
    - L, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 170: 9-11)
    - M, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 171: 1-2)
    - N, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 171: 3)
    - O, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 171: 4)
    - P, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 171: 5)
    - R, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 171: 6)
    - S, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 171: 7-8)
    - T, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 171: 9)
    - V, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 171: 10)